<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>marketing on SEO with Charan.com</title>
    <link>https://seowithcharan.com/tags/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in marketing on SEO with Charan.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {Charandeep Kapoor, 2020}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 21:04:19 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://seowithcharan.com/tags/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Oyo Tinder</title>
      <link>https://seowithcharan.com/blog/oyo-tinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 21:04:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seowithcharan.com/blog/oyo-tinder/</guid>
      <description>How long is it going to be when someone finally comes up with a simple but genius idea of collaborating OYO Rooms and Tinder?
And while you&amp;rsquo;re at it, maybe get in Manforce and Durex too?
Not all ideas have to be complicated, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jio Meet vs Zoom</title>
      <link>https://seowithcharan.com/blog/jio-meet-vs-zoom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 20:39:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seowithcharan.com/blog/jio-meet-vs-zoom/</guid>
      <description>JioMeet vs. Zoom: A poor copy Or a brilliant marketing tactic? Many of you made memes of it and called it a copy.
And many of you tried to defend the move.
But with all the publicity it has already received, I don&amp;rsquo;t think Jio has to spend another penny in advertising.
And anyway, wasn&amp;rsquo;t U.G.C. always the best form of marketing? 😝
PS: Just waiting for a tweet from Mukesh Dhirubhai Ambani &amp;ldquo;Honestly, I did it for the memes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Your Popcorn</title>
      <link>https://seowithcharan.com/blog/find-your-popcorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 20:31:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seowithcharan.com/blog/find-your-popcorn/</guid>
      <description>Ever wondered why popcorn is priced 10x more expensive at movie theatres?
Movie theatres earn only 5% revenue from ticket sales, most of the money you pay as ticket fees goes to the filmmakers.So how do movie theatres earn money?
The simple answer-Popcorn!
And hotdogs and burgers and cola and everything else they sell at 10x its original price.
They ban you from bringing in food from outside, and sell their own products at inflated prices to drive tons of revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Fake 20s Made Millions</title>
      <link>https://seowithcharan.com/blog/fake-20-made-millions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 20:29:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seowithcharan.com/blog/fake-20-made-millions/</guid>
      <description>The fake 20$ marketing campaign that made millions: A landmowing company in the USA found a very innovative way of advertising its services.
They did not place their advertisements on billboards, neither did they spend a fortune on TV ads.
Instead, they used a very simple trick to lure their customers.
They made fake 20$ bills, placed their company advertisements on it and placed them in front of lawns of people that needed mowing!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>